This video introduces 2D function related updates for everyone.
In the 2025.0 version, we launched the AI version of the generator, which is used to make paper samples.
Now it is further enhanced on this basis, and can support the input of real images.
Select the main menu bar 2D.
Open the version generator.
Select the clothing type according to the measurement value of the generated parameterized version.
In addition, you can also use the AI version of the generator.
It is located in the upper right corner of the generator.
Click to open a new window.
Here you can choose to enter a hint to describe the clothing you want or upload a reference picture.
From the 2025.1 version, you can choose to upload real images.
Click to switch to image options.
Click to upload the clothing you want.
After uploading, click to start generation.
CLO will automatically draw the paper sample according to the photos uploaded.
You can preview it in the window of the 2D version.
As long as the generation is completed, click to close.
You can also continue to modify the measurement value in the version generator to get close to the ideal effect.
Finally, click to create.
The paper sample will be placed in the 2D window.
Now, the simple image will be converted into a custom version of the online store image you like.
It becomes more intuitive and convenient.
Make the design more relaxed.
In the 2025.1 version, you can be more flexible.
Define the time limit and the time limit as the number point or non-number point.
The number point follows the set number rule.
The non-number point will smartly adapt to the movement of the number point.
To maintain the exact proportion of the whole paper.
Use the edit number tool to select the actual point on the sheet.
To make it easier to identify.
Now the number point edge will be displayed in green.
Right-click on one of the number points.
You can convert it to a non-number point.
The non-number point will return to the standard appearance without green highlights.
You can also select the frame or press the Shift key.
Choose multiple number points to convert.
The non-number point will change according to the number point movement.
Of course, you can also convert the point back to the number point.
So that when adjusting other points, the number point rule of this point is fixed.
Similarly, if you use the edit curve number tool.
You can also change the number point.
Then you can identify the number point of the curve point.
You can convert the curve point to a number point or a non-number point.
Through this update.
Users can control the number point more accurately.
In the previous version.
The inner line on the symmetrical board cannot be directly aligned to the symmetrical axis.
You have to manually move the starting point of the line section to the symmetrical axis.
A new option has been added in the 2025.1 version.
You can align the inner line to the symmetrical axis.
To make the edit version more convenient.
Use the edit version tool.
Right-click on one of the points near the symmetrical axis on the inner line.
Select align.
Select the new option below to the symmetrical axis.
The selected point will extend to the symmetrical axis at this time.
The point on the other side remains unchanged.
Then right-click on the point on the other side.
You can choose to align it to the outside of the board.
Extend the inner line to the outside of the board.
In addition, you can also directly right-click on the inner line.
Select align to the symmetrical axis.
You will find that the two ends of the internal line at this time.
Will be extended to the symmetrical axis and the outside of the board.
This update makes editing the inner line of the symmetrical board.
Become more convenient and efficient.
In the previous version.
For use on the symmetrical board.
Between the lines.
The inner line of the inner line function is generated.
If you want to align it to the symmetrical axis.
You need to manually adjust the end point of the line to the symmetrical axis.
Now a new option has been added.
You can set the inner line generated.
Extend to the symmetrical axis of the board.
Press Shift to select the middle line and the bottom curve at the same time.
On the selected line.
On the line, right-click and select.
Between the lines.
The inner line is generated to open the window.
You can see in the pop-up window.
A new option has been added at the bottom.
Align to the symmetrical axis.
When this option is randomly not opened.
The inner line is the same as before.
Extended to the outside of the board.
When you open the option of aligning to the symmetrical axis.
The inner line will align to the symmetrical axis.
Press confirm to see the result.
You can see the inner line generated on the selected side of the symmetrical board.
The other side will also be generated at the same time.
And two inner lines are based on the symmetrical axis.
Now in version 2025.1.
Users can make more flexible decisions.
Based on the extension of the inner line generated by two lines.
In version 2025.1.
You can now set the default cutout type and length.
To meet your specific requirements.
Find the main menu bar.
Set user default 2D.
Here you can set the cutout display.
Fixed screen length or actual length.
And select the cutout type you like.
As default options.
Select the display type.
Fixed screen length.
Then select the cutout type V.
Use the cutout tool to add a cutout.
Note that when selecting the fixed screen length.
The length will be adjusted by adjusting the screen.
And the length set in the property editor is not editable.
Open the default window again.
If you select the actual length.
It means that the cutout length is fixed to the set.
Enter the actual length 5mm. Set the cutout type I.
Use the cutout tool to select the cutout to be added.
You can modify the length in the property editor.
By setting the default cutout type and length update.
Users do not need to manually adjust the size and type of the cutout.
Hope this update can help you to use the cutout more conveniently.